https://www.bisok.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – BIS, Inc. - Solving Data Extraction & Integration Problems
Skip to content
GrooperGrooper PlatformGrooper FeaturesDocument Data Capture – Manage fleets of scanners and maintain consistently accurate image qualityImage Processing – Prepare images for optimal OCROCR – Our patented OCR process generates the most accurate text from images and filesDocument Management – Easily process content between multiple sourcesDocument Classification – Automate intelligent grouping of content and documentsNatural Language Processing – Learn how Grooper locates certain sentences or other language elementsData Integration Tools – Code-free integration makes getting data out of your electronic files a snapInfrastructure – Parallel processing and monitoring tools allow for fast and easy system managementTransparent AI – Open system design ensures no mystery results and helps train users CloseTrainingGrooper WikiGrooper XChangeWebinars & Video CloseStrategyTechnology and Service ProvidersMortgage & Lease Processing Providers – Enhance cooperative values and digital strategy, and increase customer satisfactionFintech AI & Data Providers – Use the power of AI to augment software and workflows, and integrate deep dataHealthcare Technology Providers – Improve revenue and payment cycle management processes, claims processing, and moreContract Lifecycle Management Solutions – Enhance services and find new opportunities by advancing analytics reportingBusiness Process Outsourcing Firms – Standardize, scale, and drive greater value through automationCRM Software – Enable faster, more versatile solutions, and create stable, connected ecosystemsEnterprise Legal Management Solutions – Automate matter life cycle, document, contract, and risk management CloseInvoice AutomationInvoice Processing Services – Extract more data at higher volumes & efficiency than any other invoice service CloseDigital OilfieldCOVID-19 Forms ProcessingFor Analytics & BI PlatformsIntegrate Unstructured Data – Integrate unstructured data from natural language documents and from dynamically changing formsAugmented Analytics – Improve Decision Making by Leveraging the Data Once Thought of as ‘Inaccessible’Add Deeper Data Discovery – Save valuable time – identify and classify information in data silos and file storesEasily Merge External Data – Increase data accuracy by integrating external database information during extraction CloseData Science WorkbenchData Cleansing Tools – Automate high quality data cleansing and integration with one solutionText Classification – Save Crucial Time in Organizing Text and DataText Extraction – Transform Your Enterprise with Faster Operations and Better ServicesMachine Learning Tools – Increase Your Operational Efficiency through a Proven, Trainable PlatformAugmented Analytics – Improve Decision Making by Leveraging the Data Once Thought of as ‘Inaccessible’ CloseData Processing ServicesDocument Scanning Services – Learn about our world-class scanning services Close CloseUser ExperienceImplementation TeamClient Relations CloseFree ResourcesResource LibraryWhite Papers – Helpful hints, tips, resources, and research to help guide your journeyBrochures – Learn more about BIS products and servicesSpotlights – Mini use-cases focused on business process improvements with GrooperWebinars – View upcoming and previously recorded webinars CloseCase StudiesBlogEventsBecome a BIS Insider CloseCompanyAbout UsCareersPartnersTechnology Partners – Recognizing technology partners who play a part in our successPartner with Us – Tired of other solutions that leave a lot to be desired? You’re not alone.Partners – Innovation driven by visionaries and excellent partner resources ClosePress ReleasesContact Us CloseLet’s Get Started!
Search for:
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy defines, documents, communicates and assigns accountability for how BIS collects, uses and manages information submitted at www.bisok.com. BIS does not sell user or client information. BIS is committed to respecting and protecting privacy rights while visiting www.bisok.com, www.grooper.com, BIS’s Grooper software user forum (“Grooper x Change”) and BIS’s blogs (“VIA,” etc.), collectively “BIS’s website” or simply “the website.” Unless otherwise posted on a specific webpage visited, this Privacy Policy explains your rights and expectations of privacy while visiting any webpage of the website.
Information Collected
Certain webpages of this website may ask you to voluntarily provide information in a form interface that personally identifies you (“personal information”). Such personal information may include your name, age, phone number, street address and e-mail address. BIS will specifically describe what information is required in order to respond or provide you with the information or service you have requested. You may also browse the website without registering or providing any such personal information.
Employment applications and related information submitted by applicants are handled by one or more third parties, reachable by links found at www.bisok.com. BIS itself does not directly collect, use or retain personal information of its applicants, except for limited contact information for the sole purpose of processing applications.
Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy, BIS does not directly collect, use, share or retain personal information of its clients or their customers, except for information limited to contact information for the sole purpose of billing and other administrative functions, or otherwise volunteered. BIS strives to not disclose any client information to third parties without implicit or explicit consent. BIS has implemented state of the art physical, administrative and technical controls in order to protect client information against unauthorized access both online and offline. Any personal or sensitive data is stored in a secure data center dedicated to safekeeping and accessed only by necessary employees.
Additionally, clients who store in BIS’s facilities any documents, data and other information that may contain confidential and/or personal information do so with the understanding that BIS is contractually obligated and strives at its utmost to protect such information with the same physical, administrative and technical controls. Continuous compliance with and monitoring of privacy policies and procedures are enforced in order to prevent and/or address any privacy-related complaints and disputes.
IP Addresses
This website may also collect anonymous data that cannot be traced to a specific individual without the cooperation of their Internet Service Provider (ISP). This includes information about IP addresses, referral data (which website or webpage “linked” to BIS’s website) and browser information. This sent data is passively accepted at the time a user requests a file from BIS’s server. BIS records IP addresses as necessary to run the website, provide services, troubleshoot problems and monitor usage.
Cookies
In order to provide the best user experience possible, BIS’s website and any applicable website hosting service or diagnostics company uses “cookies,” bits of data sent to your browser, which may then be stored in a “cache” on your computer, tablet or cellphone as small text files. These text files are not programs and are not malicious. BIS cannot access cookies sent by other websites. Additionally, BIS cannot learn your e-mail address or any other personal information from cookies.
Why?
BIS uses cookies in order to track and analyze usage of the website and further enhance and personalize your experience when you visit BIS’s website. Cookies help BIS run and improve its website as intended (including speed and security). Cookies also allow and improve potential marketing by BIS.
BIS does NOT use cookies to collect or share any personally identifiable information (PII), payment info or any other sensitive information (without your express permission), pass data to advertising networks, nor offer click rewards or commissions.
By tracking and analyzing usage, BIS can determine the best and most popular features of the website. Ultimately, cookies enable a more enhanced and personalized experience. The information is used to keep BIS’s website fresh and relevant. Cookies may also save you time when entering your name, e-mail address or other information.
Declining the Use of Cookies
You control consent to the use of cookies and you may reject cookies through your browser settings, however, access to some portions of the website and some desirable features may require cookies.
Use of Personal Information
BIS believes in protecting your privacy and will not share personal information with third parties outside of BIS, except as described in this Privacy Policy. Sharing this information helps BIS improve your experience. BIS and its support partners may use personal information to analyze website usage statistics in order to improve and personalize marketing efforts, content, layout, and offerings. If provided, BIS may also use personal information such as your name, e-mail address or mailing address to contact you regarding products and/or services that may be of interest to you or to respond to inquiries, comments and suggestions. While BIS believes these offerings will benefit you and enhance your experience, you may at any time choose to opt out from receiving such communications, either by unsubscribing or opting out of specific offerings or by deleting your profile completely.
BIS may also use specific and/or aggregated personal information along with third party data to provide you with product and content offerings of interest. BIS also may disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to potential partners and for other lawful purposes.
BIS may have arrangements with third-party service providers, vendors, or partners. When you sign up for a service, BIS may be required to share personal information with such service providers. Such third-party providers are not authorized by BIS to retain or use personal information for any purpose unrelated to providing such services.
BIS also reserves the right to disclose personal information in order to comply with law enforcement or cooperate with investigations of purported unlawful activities, misuse or abuse of this website or in connection with unauthorized or unlicensed BIS sales, etc. The personal information collected at this website may be indefinitely retained and electronically archived so long as it is secured and maintained in a manner compliant with BIS’s Privacy Policy.
Third Parties and Links to Other Sites / Materials
Information entered at the website is retrieved directly by BIS unless otherwise noted on the website or this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and dissemination of information that the website collects from you. BIS encourages users to be aware when they leave this website that other privacy policies and collection of personal information may apply. If you disclose any information to other parties through links to other websites or third-party services, different policies may apply, and BIS shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of such information. BIS does not necessarily endorse companies or related products or services which may be found linked on BIS’s website. If you decide to access any such third-party websites, you do so entirely at your own risk. BIS hereby disclaims any rights to trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos, copyrights, patents, domain names or any other intellectual property rights or interests of third parties.
Protection of Children
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”) applies to all commercial websites. BIS does not knowingly collect or solicit any personally identifiable information from children. In the event that BIS receives actual knowledge that BIS has collected such personal information, BIS will delete that information from the BIS database as quickly as possible. Any forms that appear on BIS’s website will not collect any information from any user knowingly under the age of 13 and no information will be stored or transmitted unless the response to “age” or “date of birth” indicates that the user is 13 years of age or older.
Updates / Changes
BIS reserves the right, at its own discretion, to update and make changes to its website and the manner in which BIS uses information passively or actively submitted through the website. Users will be aware of updates by the effective date documented near the link to this Privacy Policy. Your acceptance of cookies and continued use of the website after such updates amounts to your binding acceptance of those changes. Your use and rights will be governed by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of your visit.
Any questions, concerns or notices in regard to this Privacy Policy should be directed to Mike Rusnack, Director, Human Resources, 405-418-7457, mrusnack@bisok.com .
Give it a Try
The Grooper Experience Will Change You
Let's Get Started!
© 2000–2020 BIS, Inc. Grooper® is a registered trademark of BIS. All Rights Reserved. BIS Website
| Privacy Policy
